http://www.middlesexhealth.org/privacy-policy

Skip Navigation
COVID-19: Changes to Visitor Policy + Keeping You Safe
Middlesex Health facilities are currently closed to visitors, with several important exceptions. // CURRENT VISITOR POLICY
Middlesex Health is open and providing patient care, in-person and through Virtual Visits. We are continuing to perform all scheduled elective surgical procedures.
See how we're going above and beyond to keep you safe. // HERE FOR YOU
All surgical patients will be tested for COVID-19 prior to their procedure. A patient navigator will contact you to schedule this test.
We are asking that all patients who come to our facilities for an appointment wear a face mask. // MAKE A MASK AT HOME
ALL COVID-19 INFORMATION
Close Alert
COVID-19: Changes to Visitor Policy + Keeping You Safe
Find a Doctor
Donate
Careers
Pay a Bill
MyChart Portal
Search
Or, if you're not sure what you're looking for, you can:
Browse Specialists
Browse Primary Care
Back
Search All Conditions & Care Services
Clear
Search
Or, if you're not sure what you're looking for, you can:
Browse All Conditions & Care Services
Our Locations
Patients & Visitors
Find a Doctor
Donate
Careers
Pay a Bill
MyChart Portal
Search
Or, if you're not sure what you're looking for, you can:
Browse Specialists
Browse Primary Care
Back
Search All Conditions & Care Services
Clear
Search
Or, if you're not sure what you're looking for, you can:
Browse All Conditions & Care Services
Home
Privacy Policy
Share
Email
Print
Privacy Policy Menu:
Open Menu
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Middlesex Health Systems, Inc. respects the privacy rights of the users of the MiddlesexHealth.org website (the "Website"). Middlesex wants you to understand what information we collect from our Website users and how we use the information we collect.
PLEASE NOTE THAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT APPLY TO THE "LEARNING CENTER" SECTION OF THE WEBSITE. The Learning Center Section of the Website is operated by a third party, Mayo Foundation for Medical Education and Research ("MFMER"). When you are visiting those web pages or are submitting information on those web pages, you are submitting information directly to MFMER. However, Middlesex cares that you know what MFMER does with your information. Accordingly, MFMER has a link to its own terms of use on each page that they operate within the Website. Please review MFMER's terms of use before you share any personally identifying information within the Learning Center Section of the Website. If you would like to view the privacy policy applicable to the Learning Center Section now, please click here.
BECAUSE THE WEBSITE IS NOT TO BE USED FOR THE SOLICITATION OR RENDERING OF MEDICAL ADVICE, NOR ARE YOU PERMITTED TO DISCLOSE INDIVIDUALLY IDENTIFIABLE HEALTH INFORMATION, BE ADVISED THAT THE PRIVACY PROTECTIONS THAT GENERALLY APPLY TO COMMUNICATIONS BETWEEN A DOCTOR AND A PATIENT MAY NOT APPLY TO COMMUNICATIONS THROUGH THE WEBSITE OR EMAIL.
THE INFORMATION WE COLLECTThe information that we collect from you will depend upon your use of the Website. For example, we may require more information from a person who is using the Website to apply for a job, as opposed to a person who is merely using the search tools to find information on hospital visiting hours. Information we may collect includes: first name, last name, ZIP code, e-mail address, and birth date. As stated above, more or less information may be required depending on your use.
HOW WE USE THE INFORMATIONAll personally identifying information that Middlesex collects is used directly for customizing your visits to our site or, in the case of certain information, as a security feature that prevents others from obtaining your password. In addition, to the extent you provide us information in connection with the request for a particular service (including applying for an employment position), we will use the information in connection with the providing the service requested. In addition, we may share any information we collect with our subsidiaries and affiliates to the extent they may be involved with the Website or performing any Services we may offer or you may request or to facilitate marketing, fundraising or other communications with You.
Your e-mail address is used to send you administrative messages or other communications regarding your use of the Website. If you choose to let us do so, Middlesex and its affiliates and subsidiaries may also use your e-mail address to notify you of new features or services available on the Website or events or services available through Middlesex or its subsidiaries and affiliates or to facilitate fundraising efforts. If you do not wish to receive these e-mail notices, you may opt out of this service by clicking the "opt out" option at the bottom of the email correspondence You received.
We use your information to statistically analyze the use of our site, improve our content and product offerings, and customize the Website’s content and services to better meet your needs. Your personally identifying information is not used to monitor your activities on our site. In addition, we do not sell, trade, or rent your personally identifying information to third parties. We may, however, disclose certain non-identifying aggregated information to third parties about the users of our services.
We will not use your personally identifying information for any purpose other than as set forth herein unless we believe such disclosure is required by law or to protect our rights, or the safety or rights of other users or the public.
USE OF COOKIES Cookies are pieces of information stored directly on the device you are using. Cookies allow us to collect information such as browser type, time spent on the Website, pages visited, and language preferences. We and our service providers use the information for security purposes, to facilitate navigation, display information more effectively, and to personalize your experience while using the Website. We also use cookies to recognize your computer or device, which makes your use of the Website easier, such as to remember what is in your shopping cart. In addition, we use cookies to gather statistical information about Website usage in order to continually improve its design and functionality, understand how individuals use it, and to assist us with resolving questions regarding it. Cookies further allow us to select which of our advertisements or offers are most likely to appeal to you and display them while you are on the Website. We may also use cookies in online advertising to track consumer responses to our advertisements.You can refuse to accept these cookies by following your browser's instructions; however, if you do not accept them, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of the Website. You may also not receive advertising or other offers from us that are relevant to your interests and needs. To learn more about cookies, please visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/
Middlesex Hospital uses Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting, and HotJar to collect anonymous data about our website visitors and how they interact with the website in order to improve our marketing and user experience. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings.
USE OF IP ADDRESSESEvery Internet user is identified by a unique number known as an Internet Protocol (IP) address. If you have a static IP address, you get the same number each time you connect to the Internet. If you have a dynamic IP address, a number is assigned to your computer from a pool of addresses established by your ISP (Internet Service Provider), which can result in your computer having a different IP address each time you use the Internet. World Wide Web servers use IP addresses to identify your computer.
The Website collects IP addresses for security, system administration and reporting aggregate information. When you visit a page on the Website, our servers log your IP address, but we do not link this IP address to your personally identifying information. This means that while your activity is logged, you remain anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify users when we believe it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use, or to protect our service, Website, users, or other parties.
SECURITYUnfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed as 100 percent secure; but Middlesex uses its best commercially reasonable efforts to use the most current data security technology available to protect your information, and to continue to implement the new security methods as they become available.
LINKS TO OTHER SITESYou should be aware that when using the Website, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. For example, if you click on an advertisement or a link in a news article, you may be taken to another site. These other sites may send their own cookies to your computer, collect data, or solicit personal information from you. These other sites are not bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of such sites before disclosing any personally identifying information.
YOUR CONSENTBy using the Website, you consent to the collection and use of your information as outlined in this privacy policy. If we make changes to this policy, we will post them on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it. Changes are effective when posted to this page. Your continued use after any change is posted is an acceptance by you of such change.
QUESTIONS AND FEEDBACKIf you have any questions regarding privacy on our site, please email us at info@midhosp.org
